When Planets Collide
Collision Earth is a action, science fiction, tv
movie film directed by Paul Ziller.
A huge solar flare blasts Mercury out of it's orbit and provides it with an
intense magnetic field and it's on collision course for Earth.
Edward, played by Andrew Airlie.
Victoria, played by Diane Farr.
James, played by Kirk Acevedo.
Christopher, played by Chad Krowchuk.
Brooke, played by Jessica Parker Kennedy.
Matthew, played by Adam Greydon Reid.
Collision Earth is a  Canadian disaster television film directed by Paul Ziller.
It was released in 2011 for broadcast on the Syfy Channel and later
distributed by Anchor Bay Entertainment on Blu-ray.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.